{
    "id": "a88661e9107846aabcb9ee658ed74873",
    "title": "Linking Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was …………………… unable to attend the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in particular",
                "therefore",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………, we are satisfied with your performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "For example",
                "In general",
                "As well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not quite sure what time I will arrive, maybe half past eight or a quarter to nine. ………………… I will be there before nine o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Anyhow",
                "In particular",
                "In general"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a small house and requires a lot of repairs. …………………, it is a long way from the center.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Nonetheless",
                "In particular",
                "Moreover"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody had heard of Einstein, ………………… hardly anyone could understand his theory of relativity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "of course"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was always popular with women and even got married twice. ……………………, the women closest to him were invariably unhappy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Certainly",
                "All the same",
                "Even so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is true that the British did some good in India. ……………………, colonialism is basically bad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even so",
                "of course",
                "in particular"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me in …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anyway",
                "any way",
                "by the way"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car broke down on the way. …………………… ., I managed to reach in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Certainly",
                "Therefore",
                "In spite of this"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Interesting movie?’ ‘…………………., it was a complete waste of time’.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "On the contrary",
                "Certainly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}